Right, thusfar all I've really got in mind, in terms of a concept is the overall history of the world that the game would be set in. Hopefully later, I'll actually
manage to imagine up the actual story, and characters, and shit. Oh, and names that I haven't thought of yet, will be replaced with placeholder Greek letters. Because.
Anyway...
The game is set in the land of α. α is heavily reliant upon the power of maaaaaaggggiiiic (feel the power of it), and it serves as a way of powering machines
in the stead of electricity (I'd liken it a bit to how Lost Odyssey deals with magic, but less "this thing is a magic engine" and more that things are either
actively powered by people with the talent for magic, or has been infused with magic, so that it may perform its purpose, until its magic reserves run out).
α is a monarchy, ruled by a shadowy, and virtually unknown entity known as the Patriach. The term monarchy however is used loosely, and α is more directly ruled by
its reliance upon magic, a comodity which is predominantly controlled by what is known as The Mancery, a gigantic collective of those that have the talent for magic.
Those that have said talent, are known as Mancers.

MORE TO COME YO.